Raphael Cirelli Garrido

Front-End Web Developer

PROFILE

I've always been passionate about technology.

My first contact with programming was in 2010 in a technical course at high school.

In 2016 I graduated in Game Design at Anhembi Morumbi University - UAM.

Working for +5 years as an IT Analyst, I wanted a career change. And at the beginning of 2022, I decided to start a Web Development course at Trybe, which is one of the most recognized programming schools in Brazil.

SKILLS

- Development
 - HTML CSS JS React Redux React Router Tailwind Material UI
- Unit and Integration Testing
 - Jest React Testing Library
- Soft Skills
 - Like to solve problems Good Learner Teamplayer

EDUCATION

Web Development, *Trybe* □

Feb 2022 - Mar 2023

One of the most recognized programming schools in Brazil.

More than 1500 hours of training cover the fundamentals of web development, Front-end, Back-end, computer science, software engineering, agile methodologies, and soft skills.

Technologies: JavaScript, ES6, React, React Router, Redux, Context API, Jest, RTL, Node.JS, Express, SQL, Docker, Heroku.

Game Design Bachelor's Degree, Anhembi Morumbi - UAM 🖸

Feb 2012 - Jun 2016

Focused on game development for many platforms. I learned about level design, game theory, UI design, 3D Modelling, programming in C#, Unity engine.

CERTIFICATES

Web Development Fundamentals, *Trybe* □

1st Module of the Web Development Course

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

IT Analyst, *Theracom Solutions* □

Dec 2016 - present

- Installation and Configuration of network equipment (routers, switches,)
- Deployment and Management of a Local Server and Cloud Server
- Configuration and Management of a 3CX voip system
- Support to users

Computer Technician, *Theracom Solutions* □

Apr 2015 - Nov 2016

- · Support to users
- Maintenance and Configuration of PCs